A Guide to the Nelson A. Rockefeller, Vice Presidential records, Central Files, Series 3 FA378
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Subject File, 2
  - Meetings - Conferences (MC), 32
    - MC 1 - Domestic Forums/Los Angeles (Box 172)
    - MC 1 - Domestic Forums/Philadelphia (Box 172)
    - MC 1 - Domestic Forums/Tampa (Box 172)
    - MC 2 - National Comission on Water Quality (Box 172)
    - MC 2 - National Comission on Water Quality, 1976 February 1 (Box 172)
    - MC 3 - Presidential Panel on Federal Compensation (Box 172)
    - MC 4 - Federal Design Improvement Program (Box 172)
    - MC 5 - Domestic Council Privacy Committee Roundtable-Privacy Inf. Policy (Box 172)
    - MC 6 - White House Public Forums on Domestic Policy (Box 172)
    - MC 7 - National Center for Productivity and the Quality of Working Life (Box 172)
    - MC 8 - National Industrial Energy Council meeting-Department of Commerce (Box 172)
    - MC 9 - Energy Independence Authority (Box 172)
    - MC 10 - National conference on Regulatory Reform (Box 172)
    - MC 11 - Advisory and consulting group on "Contributions of Technology to Economic Strength" or "Anticipated Advances in Science and Technology" (Box 172)
  - Messages (ME), 33
    - ME - MESSAGES (Box 173)
    - ME - MESSAGES, 1976 (Box 173)
    - ME 1 - Furnished to Adults (messages) (Box 173)
    - ME 1 - Furnished to Adults (messages) by name/A (Box 173)
    - ME 1 - Furnished to Adults (messages) by name/B (Box 173)
    - ME 1 - Furnished to Adults (messages) by name/C (Box 173)
    - ME 1 - Furnished to Adults (messages) by name/D (Box 173)
    - ME 1 - Furnished to Adults (messages) by name/E (Box 173)
    - ME 1 - Furnished to Adults (messages) by name/F (Box 173)
    - ME 1 - Furnished to Adults (messages) by name/G (Box 173)
    - ME 1 - Furnished to Adults (messages) by name/H (Box 173)
    - ME 1 - Furnished to Adults (messages) by name/I (Box 173)
    - ME 1 - Furnished to Adults (messages) by name/J (Box 173)
    - ME 1 - Furnished to Adults (messages) by name/K (Box 173)
    - ME 1 - Furnished to Adults (messages) by name/L (Box 173)
    - ME 1 - Furnished to Adults (messages) by name/M (Box 173)
    - ME 1 - Furnished to Adults (messages) by name/N (Box 173)
    - ME 1 - Furnished to Adults (messages) by name/O (Box 173)
    - ME 1 - Furnished to Adults (messages) by name/P (Box 173)
    - ME 1 - Furnished to Adults (messages) by name/Q (Box 173)
    - ME 1 - Furnished to Adults (messages) by name/R (Box 174)
    - ME 1 - Furnished to Adults (messages) by name/S (Box 174)
    - ME 1 - Furnished to Adults (messages) by name/T (Box 174)
    - ME 1 - Furnished to Adults (messages) by name/U (Box 174)
    - ME 1 - Furnished to Adults (messages) by name/V (Box 174)
    - ME 1 - Furnished to Adults (messages) by name/W (Box 174)
    - ME 1 - Furnished to Adults (messages) by name/X (Box 174)
    - ME 1 - Furnished to Adults (messages) by name/Y (Box 174)
    - ME 1 - Furnished to Adults (messages) by name/Z (Box 174)
    - ME 1-1 - Wedding Anniversaries by name/A-C (Box 174)
    - ME 1-1 - Wedding Anniversaries by name/D-J (Box 174)
    - ME 1-1 - Wedding Anniversaries by name/K-Q (Box 174)
    - ME 1-1 - Wedding Anniversaries by name/R-Z (Box 174)
    - ME 1-2 - Birthday Greetings by name/A (Box 174)
    - ME 1-2 - Birthday Greetings by name/B (Box 174)
    - ME 1-2 - Birthday Greetings by name/C (Box 174)
    - ME 1-2 - Birthday Greetings by name/D (Box 174)
    - ME 1-2 - Birthday Greetings by name/E (Box 174)
    - ME 1-2 - Birthday Greetings by name/F (Box 174)
    - ME 1-2 - Birthday Greetings by name/G (Box 174)
    - ME 1-2 - Birthday Greetings by name/H (Box 174)
    - ME 1-2 - Birthday Greetings by name/I (Box 174)
    - ME 1-2 - Birthday Greetings by name/J (Box 174)
    - ME 1-2 - Birthday Greetings by name/K (Box 174)
    - ME 1-2 - Birthday Greetings by name/L (Box 174)
    - ME 1-2 - Birthday Greetings by name/M (Box 174)
    - ME 1-2 - Birthday Greetings by name/N (Box 174)
    - ME 1-2 - Birthday Greetings by name/O (Box 174)
    - ME 1-2 - Birthday Greetings by name/P (Box 174)
    - ME 1-2 - Birthday Greetings by name/Q-R (Box 174)
    - ME 1-2 - Birthday Greetings by name/S (Box 174)
    - ME 1-2 - Birthday Greetings by name/T (Box 174)
    - ME 1-2 - Birthday Greetings by name/U-V (Box 174)
    - ME 1-2 - Birthday Greetings by name/W (Box 174)
    - ME 1-2 - Birthday Greetings by name/X,Y,Z (Box 174)
    - ME 1-2 - Birthday Greetings by name/ (Box 174)
    - ME 1-2 - Birthday Greetings by name/ (Box 174)
    - ME 1-2-1 - Birth Announcement congratulations (Box 175)
    - ME 1-2-1 - Birth Announcement congratulations by name/A-Z (Box 175)
    - ME 1-3 - Sympathy-Condolences-illness-death (Box 175)
    - ME 1-3 - Sympathy-Condolences-illness-death by name/A-G (Box 175)
    - ME 1-3 - Sympathy-Condolences-illness-death by name/H-Z (Box 175)
    - ME 2 - Message to Children (Box 175)
    - ME 2 - Message to Children by name/A-Z (Box 175)
    - ME 3 - Organization-Messages (Box 175)
    - ME 3 - Organization-Messages by name/A (Box 175)
    - ME 3 - Organization-Messages by name/B (Box 175)
    - ME 3 - Organization-Messages by name/C (Box 175)
    - ME 3 - Organization-Messages by name/D (Box 175)
    - ME 3 - Organization-Messages by name/E (Box 175)
    - ME 3 - Organization-Messages by name/F (Box 175)
    - ME 3 - Organization-Messages by name/G (Box 175)
    - ME 3 - Organization-Messages by name/H (Box 175)
    - ME 3 - Organization-Messages by name/I (Box 175)
    - ME 3 - Organization-Messages by name/J (Box 175)
    - ME 3 - Organization-Messages by name/K (Box 175)
    - ME 3 - Organization-Messages by name/L (Box 175)
    - ME 3 - Organization-Messages by name/M (Box 175)
    - ME 3 - Organization-Messages by name/N (Box 175)
    - ME 3 - Organization-Messages by name/O (Box 175)
    - ME 3 - Organization-Messages by name/P (Box 175)
    - ME 3 - Organization-Messages by name/Q-R (Box 175)
    - ME 3 - Organization-Messages by name/S (Box 175)
    - ME 3 - Organization-Messages by name/T (Box 175)
    - ME 3 - Organization-Messages by name/U-V (Box 175)
    - ME 3 - Organization-Messages by name/W (Box 175)
    - ME 3 - Organization-Messages by name/X,Y,Z (Box 175)
    - ME 3-1 - Churches (messages)/A-Z (Box 176)
    - ME 3-1-1 - Catholic/A-Z (Box 176)
    - ME 3-1-2 - Jewish/A-Z (Box 176)
    - ME 3-1-3 - Protestant/A-Z (Box 176)
    - ME 3-2 - Colleges, Universities or Schools/A-G (Box 176)
    - ME 3-2 - Colleges, Universities or Schools/H-M (Box 176)
    - ME 3-2 - Colleges, Universities or Schools/N-Z (Box 176)
    - ME 3-3 - Governmental Groups (Box 176)
    - ME 3-3 - Governmental Groups/A-L (Box 176)
    - ME 3-3 - Governmental Groups/M-Z (Box 176)
    - ME 3-4 - Hospitals/A-Z (Box 176)
    - ME 3-5 - Labor Groups/A-Z (Box 176)
    - ME 3-6 - Newspapers Magazines, Radio, TV (Box 176)
    - ME 3-6 - Newspapers Magazines, Radio, TV/A-Z (Box 176)
    - ME 3-7 - Trade Fairs, Fairs, Exhibits (Box 176)
    - ME 4 - Messages denied (Box 176)
    - ME 4-3 - Messages denied to Organizations/A-Z (Box 176)
    - ME 4-3-6 - Messages denied to Newspapers, Magazines, Radio, TV/A-Z (Box 176)
  - National Security/Defense (ND), 34
    - ND - NATIONAL SECURITY/DEFENSE (Box 176)
    - ND 1 - Aircraft (Box 176)
    - ND 2 - Civil Defense (Box 176)
    - ND 2-1 - Civil Defense Plans (Box 176)
    - ND 3 - Communications-Electronics (Box 176)
    - ND 4 - Defense Mobilization (Box 176)
    - ND 6 - Intelligence (Box 176)
    - ND 6-1 - Sabotage-Espionage (Box 176)
    - ND 6-2 - Subversive Activities Control (Box 176)
    - ND 8 - Military Personnel (Box 176)
    - ND 8 - Military Personnel by individual/A-Z (Box 176)
    - ND 8-3 - Conscription-Induction-Draft-Training-Deferment (Box 176)
    - ND 8-6 - Pay-Allowance-Pensions (Box 176)
    - ND 8-8 - Separations-Discharges-Retirements (Box 176)
    - ND 10 - Properties-Installations (Box 176)
    - ND 12 - Reserve Forces and National Guard (Box 176)
    - ND 13 - Security (military) (Box 176)
    - ND 13-3 - Classified Information (Box 176)
    - ND 13-4 - Personnel (Box 176)
    - ND 14 - Service Schools (Box 176)
    - ND 14-1 - Air Academy (Box 176)
    - ND 14-4 - Coast Guard Academy (Box 176)
    - ND 14-6 - Merchant Marine Academy (Box 176)
    - ND 14-7 - Military Academy (Box 176)
    - ND 14-9 - Naval Academy (Box 176)
    - ND 15 - Ships-Submarines (Box 176)
    - ND 16 - Supply-Logistics (Box 176)
    - ND 18 - Wars (Box 176)
    - ND 18 - Wars by name of war or country/A-Z (Box 176)
    - ND 18-1 - Casualties (Box 176)
    - ND 18-2 - Displaced Persons-Refugees (Box 176)
    - ND 18-3 - Prisoners (Box 176)
    - ND 19-3 - Terror Groups (Box 176)
    - ND 20 - Weapons-Ordnance-Munitions (Box 176)
    - ND 20-1 - International Agreements (Box 176)
    - ND 21-1 - Army (Box 176)
    - ND 21-2 - Navy (Box 176)
    - ND 21-3 - Air Force (Box 176)
    - ND 21-4 - Marines (Box 176)
    - ND 21-5 - Coast Guard (Box 176)
  - Natural Resources (NR), 35
    - NR - Natural Resources (Box 177)
    - NR 2 - Energy (Box 177)
    - NR 2 - Energy, 1975 July (Box 177)
    - NR 2 - Energy, 1975 October (Box 177)
    - NR 2 - Energy, 1975 November (Box 177)
    - NR 2 - Energy, 1976 January (Box 177)
    - NR 2 - Energy, 1976 April (Box 177)
    - NR 2 - Energy, 1976 June (Box 177)
    - NR 2-1 - Crisis (Energy) (Box 177)
    - NR 2-2 - Minerals - Metals (Box 177)
    - NR 2-3 - Oil (Natural Gas) (Box 177)
    - NR 2-3-1 - Naval Petroleum Reserves (Box 177)
    - NR 3 - Fish - Wildlife (Box 177)
    - NR 5 - Land (Box 177)
    - NR 6 - Rivers (Box 177)
    - NR 6-1 - Projects (River-Water-Harbor) (Box 177)
  - Outer Space (OS), 36
    - OS - Outer Space (Box 178)
    - OS 3 - Space Flight (Box 178)
    - OS 3-1 - Astronauts (Box 178)
    - OS 4 - Space Research (Box 178)
  - Parks - Monuments (PA), 37
    - PA - PARKS - MONUMENTS (Box 178)
    - PA 2 - Memorials - Monuments (Box 178)
    - PA 3- Parks - Reservations (Box 178)
  - Peace (PC), 38
    - PC - PEACE (Box 178)
    - PC 4 - Medical Assistance Programs (Box 178)
  - Personnel Management (Civil Service) (PE), 39
    - PE - PERSONNEL MANAGEMENT (Civil Service) (Box 178)
    - PE 1 - Employee Relations - Activities (Box 178)
    - PE 1-1 - Blood Banks (Box 178)
    - PE 1-2 - Political Activities (Box 178)
    - PE 2 - Employment - Appointments (Box 178)
    - PE 2 - Employment - Appointments, 1975 May (Box 178)
    - PE 2 - Employment - Appointments, 1975 July (Box 178)
    - PE 2 - Employment - Appointments, 1975 August (Box 178)
    - PE 2 - Employment - Appointments, 1975 November (Box 178)
    - PE 2 - Employment - Appointments, 1976 January (Box 178)
    - PE 2 - Employment - Appointments, 1976 February (Box 178)
    - PE 2 - Employment - Appointments, 1976 March (Box 178)
    - PE 2 - Employment - Appointments, 1976 April (Box 178)
    - PE 2 - Employment - Appointments, 1976 July (Box 178)
    - PE 2-1 - Schedule C (Employment) (Box 179)
    - PE 3 - Fair Employment (Box 179)
    - PE 7 - Investigations (Box 179)
    - PE 8 - Leave (Box 179)
    - PE 10 - Payrolls - Deductions (Box 179)
    - PE 11 - Retirement System and Pay (Box 179)
    - PE 12 - Salaries - Wages (Box 179)
    - PE 12-2 - Congressional (Box 179)
    - PE 12-3 - Federal Civil Service Employees (Box 179)
    - PE 12-4 - Judicial (Box 179)
    - PE 12-6 - Vice President (Box 179)
    - PE 13 - Separations form Government Employees (Box 179)
    - PE 14 - Training - Orientation (Government Employees) (Box 179)
    - PE 15 - Travel - Moving Expenses - Per Diem (Box 179)
    - PE 16 - Conduct of Government Employees (Box 179)
  - Political Affairs (PL), 40
    - PL - POLITICAL AFFAIRS (Box 179)
    - PL - POLITICAL AFFAIRS, 1975 August (Box 179)
    - PL - POLITICAL AFFAIRS, 1976 January (Box 179)
    - PL - POLITICAL AFFAIRS, 1976 May (Box 179)
    - PL - POLITICAL AFFAIRS, 1976 July (Box 179)
    - PL - POLITICAL AFFAIRS/A-Z (by state name) (Box 179)
    - PL 1 - Conventions (Box 179)
    - PL 1-1 - Delegates (Box 179)
    - PL 1-2 - Platforms (Box 179)
    - PL 1-3 - Site Selection (Box 179)
    - PL 1-4 - Tickets (Box 179)
    - PL 2 - Fund Raising - Expenditures (Box 179)
    - PL 2 - Fund Raising - Expenditures, 1976 January (Box 179)
    - PL 3 - Political Message (Box 179)
    - PL 3 - Political Message/A-Z (by state name) (Box 179)
    - PL 4 - Patronage (Box 179)
    - PL 5 - Political Parties (Box 179)
    - PL 5-2 - Democratic Party (Box 179)
    - PL 5-4 - Republican Party (Box 179)
    - PL 6 - Publicity - Publications (Box 179)
    - PL 7 - Speakers (Box 179)
    - PL 8 - Volunteers (Box 179)
    - PL 9 - Voting (Box 179)
    - PL 10 - Women (Box 179)
    - PL 11 - Support for the Vice President as a Presidential Candidate (Box 180)
    - PL 11 - Support for the Vice President as a Presidential Candidate, 1975 November 18 (Box 180)
    - PL 11 - Support for the Vice President as a Presidential Candidate, 1975 November 19 (Box 180)
    - PL 11 - Support for the Vice President as a Presidential Candidate, 1975 November 20 (Box 180)
    - PL 11 - Support for the Vice President as a Presidential Candidate, 1975 November 21 (Box 180)
    - PL 11 - Support for the Vice President as a Presidential Candidate, 1975 November 24 (Box 180)
    - PL 11 - Support for the Vice President as a Presidential Candidate, 1975 November 25 (Box 180)
    - PL 11 - Support for the Vice President as a Presidential Candidate, 1975 November 26 (Box 180)
    - PL 11 - Support for the Vice President as a Presidential Candidate, 1975 November 28 (Box 180)
    - PL 11 - Support for the Vice President as a Presidential Candidate, 1975 December 1 (Box 180)
    - PL 11 - Support for the Vice President as a Presidential Candidate, 1975 December 2 (Box 180)
    - PL 11 - Support for the Vice President as a Presidential Candidate, 1975 December 3 (Box 180)
    - PL 11 - Support for the Vice President as a Presidential Candidate, 1975 December 9 (Box 180)
    - PL 11 - Support for the Vice President as a Presidential Candidate, 1975 December 10 (Box 180)
    - PL 11 - Support for the Vice President as a Presidential Candidate, 1975 December 12 (Box 180)
    - PL 11 - Support for the Vice President as a Presidential Candidate, 1975 December 15 (Box 180)
    - PL 11 - Support for the Vice President as a Presidential Candidate, 1975 December 16 (Box 180)
    - PL 11 - Support for the Vice President as a Presidential Candidate, 1975 December 17 (Box 180)
    - PL 11 - Support for the Vice President as a Presidential Candidate, 1975 December 25 (Box 180)
    - PL 11 - Support for the Vice President as a Presidential Candidate, 1976 January 1 (Box 181)
    - PL 11 - Support for the Vice President as a Presidential Candidate, 1976 January 9 (Box 181)
    - PL 11 - Support for the Vice President as a Presidential Candidate, 1976 January 10 (Box 181)
    - PL 11 - Support for the Vice President as a Presidential Candidate, 1976 January 21 (Box 181)
    - PL 11 - Support for the Vice President as a Presidential Candidate, 1976 February 1 (Box 181)
    - PL 11 - Support for the Vice President as a Presidential Candidate, 1976 March 1 (Box 181)
    - PL 11 - Support for the Vice President as a Presidential Candidate, 1976 March 9 (Box 181)
    - PL 11 - Support for the Vice President as a Presidential Candidate, 1976 April (Box 181)
    - PL 11 - Support for the Vice President as a Presidential Candidate, 1976 May (Box 181)
    - PL 11 - Support for the Vice President as a Presidential Candidate, 1976 June 1 (Box 181)
    - PL 11 - Support for the Vice President as a Presidential Candidate, 1976 June 15 (Box 181)
    - PL 11 - Support for the Vice President as a Presidential Candidate, 1976 July (Box 181)
    - PL 11 - Support for the Vice President as a Presidential Candidate, 1976 August (Box 181)
    - PL 11 - Support for the Vice President as a Presidential Candidate, 1976 September (Box 181)
  - Postal Service (PO), 41
    - PO - POSTAL SERVICE (Box 181)
    - PO 2 - Commemorative Stamps - Gift Albums (Box 181)
    - PO 3 - Rates - Fees - Special Services (Box 181)
  - President (Personal) (PP), 42
    - PP - PRESIDENT (PERSONAL) (Box 181)
    - PP 5 - Family (Box 181)
    - PP 10-3 - Private Dinner (Box 181)
    - PP 10-4 - Private Reception (Box 181)
  - Procurement - Disposal (PQ), 43
    - PQ - Procurement - Disposal (Box 181)
    - PQ 1 - Disposing - Excess - Surplus (Box 181)
    - PQ 2 - Purchasing - Contracting - Procuring (Box 181)
  - Public Relations (PR), 44
    - PR - PUBLIC RELATIONS (Box 181)
    - PR 1 - Administration Appreciation letters (Box 181)
    - PR 2 - Administration Complaints-Criticism (Box 181)
    - PR 3 - Administration Support - Offer of Service (Box 182)
    - PR 3 - Administration Support - Offer of Service, 1975 June (Box 182)
    - PR 3 - Administration Support - Offer of Service, 1975 August (Box 182)
    - PR 3 - Administration Support - Offer of Service, 1975 September (Box 182)
    - PR 3 - Administration Support - Offer of Service, 1975 November (Box 182)
    - PR 3 - Administration Support - Offer of Service, 1976 January (Box 182)
    - PR 3 - Administration Support - Offer of Service, 1976 May (Box 182)
    - PR 5 - Autographs - Photographs - Holographs (Box 182)
    - PR 5-1 - Photo Requests Granted (Box 182)
    - PR 5-1 - Photo Requests Granted, 1976 January (Box 182)
    - PR 5-1 - Photo Requests Granted/A (by name) (Box 182)
    - PR 5-1 - Photo Requests Granted/B (by name) (Box 182)
    - PR 5-1 - Photo Requests Granted/C (by name) (Box 182)
    - PR 5-1 - Photo Requests Granted/D (by name) (Box 182)
    - PR 5-1 - Photo Requests Granted/E (by name) (Box 182)
    - PR 5-1 - Photo Requests Granted/F (by name) (Box 182)
    - PR 5-1 - Photo Requests Granted/G (by name) (Box 182)
    - PR 5-1 - Photo Requests Granted/H (by name) (Box 182)
    - PR 5-1 - Photo Requests Granted/I (by name) (Box 182)
    - PR 5-1 - Photo Requests Granted/J (by name) (Box 182)
    - PR 5-1 - Photo Requests Granted/K (by name) (Box 182)
    - PR 5-1 - Photo Requests Granted/L (by name) (Box 182)
    - PR 5-1 - Photo Requests Granted/M (by name) (Box 182)
    - PR 5-1 - Photo Requests Granted/N (by name) (Box 182)
    - PR 5-1 - Photo Requests Granted/O (by name) (Box 182)
    - PR 5-1 - Photo Requests Granted/P (by name) (Box 182)
    - PR 5-1 - Photo Requests Granted/Q (by name) (Box 182)
    - PR 5-1 - Photo Requests Granted/R (by name) (Box 182)
    - PR 5-1 - Photo Requests Granted/S (by name) (Box 182)
    - PR 5-1 - Photo Requests Granted/T (by name) (Box 182)
    - PR 5-1 - Photo Requests Granted/U-V (by name) (Box 182)
    - PR 5-1 - Photo Requests Granted/W (by name) (Box 182)
    - PR 5-1 - Photo Requests Granted/X, Y, Z (by name) (Box 182)
    - PR 5-2 - Photo Requests Denied (Box 182)
    - PR 5-3 - Holographs - Vice President - Handwriting (Box 182)
    - PR 6 - Contests - Essays (Box 182)
    - PR 7 - Engagements - Appointments - Interviews (Box 183)
    - PR 7-1 - Appointments granted (Box 183)
    - PR 7-1 - Appointments granted/A-Z (Box 183)
    - PR 7-2 - Appointements denied (Box 183)
    - PR 7-2 - Appointements denied/A-E (Box 183)
    - PR 7-2 - Appointements denied/F-O (Box 183)
    - PR 7-2 - Appointements denied/P-Z (Box 183)
    - PR 7-3 - Vice Presidents Schedule (Box 183)
    - PR 7-3 - Vice Presidents Schedule, 1975 November 1 (Box 183)
    - PR 7-3 - Vice Presidents Schedule, 1976 January 1 (Box 183)
    - PR 7-3 - Vice Presidents Schedule, 1976 June 1 (Box 183)
    - PR 8 - Exhibits - Fairs - Expositions (Box 183)
    - PR 9 - Graphics, maps, charts, posters (Box 183)
    - PR 10 - Lists of names - mailing lists (Box 183)
    - PR 11 - Motion Pictures - Film Strips (Box 183)
    - PR 12 - Petitions-Resolutions-Multiple Sign. (Box 183)
    - PR 12 - Petitions-Resolutions-Multiple Sign./State (Box 183)
    - PR 13 - Public Opinion Polls (Box 183)
    - PR 14 (Box 184)
    - PR 14-1 (Box 184)
    - PR 14-1, 1975 July 1 (Box 184)
    - PR 14-1, 1975 August 1 (Box 184)
    - PR 14-1, 1976 January 1 (Box 184)
    - PR 14-1, 1976 June 1 (Box 184)
    - PR 14-2 (Box 184)
    - PR 14-2, 1975 December 1 (Box 184)
    - PR 14-2, 1976 January 1 (Box 184)
    - PR 14-2-1 (Box 184)
    - PR 15 (Box 184)
    - PR 16 (Box 184)
    - PR 16, 1976 January 1 (Box 184)
    - PR 16-1 (Box 184)
    - PR 16-1, 1976 March 1 (Box 184)
    - A, 1976 June 1 (Box 184)
    - PR 16-2 - Contributions-Donations-Personal loans-Auction gifts (Box 185)
    - PR 16-2 - Contributions-Donations-Personal loans-Auction gifts, 1975 April 1 (Box 185)
    - PR 16-2 - Contributions-Donations-Personal loans-Auction gifts, 1975 May 1 (Box 185)
    - PR 16-2 - Contributions-Donations-Personal loans-Auction gifts, 1975 June 1 (Box 185)
    - PR 16-2 - Contributions-Donations-Personal loans-Auction gifts, 1975 July 1 (Box 185)
    - PR 16-2 - Contributions-Donations-Personal loans-Auction gifts, 1975 August 1 (Box 185)
    - PR 16-2 - Contributions-Donations-Personal loans-Auction gifts, 1975 September 1 (Box 185)
    - PR 16-2 - Contributions-Donations-Personal loans-Auction gifts, 1975 October 1 (Box 185)
    - PR 16-2 - Contributions-Donations-Personal loans-Auction gifts, 1975 November 1 (Box 185)
    - PR 16-2 - Contributions-Donations-Personal loans-Auction gifts, 1975 December 1 (Box 185)
    - PR 16-2 - Contributions-Donations-Personal loans-Auction gifts, 1976 January 1 (Box 185)
    - PR 16-2 - Contributions-Donations-Personal loans-Auction gifts, 1976 February 1 (Box 185)
    - PR 16-2 - Contributions-Donations-Personal loans-Auction gifts, 1976 March (Box 185)
    - PR 16-2 - Contributions-Donations-Personal loans-Auction gifts, 1976 April (Box 185)
    - PR 16-2 - Contributions-Donations-Personal loans-Auction gifts, 1976 May (Box 185)
    - PR 16-2 - Contributions-Donations-Personal loans-Auction gifts, 1976 July (Box 185)
    - PR 16-2 - Contributions-Donations-Personal loans-Auction gifts, 1976 September (Box 185)
    - PR 16-4 - Entertainment-performances for Vice President (Box 186)
    - PR 16-5 - Excerpts-quoting-misquoting Vice President (Box 186)
    - PR 16-6 - Forwards (Box 186)
    - PR 16-8 - Opinions-Statements-Questions or Articles (Box 186)
    - PR 16-8 - Opinions-Statements-Questions or Articles, 1975 September 1 (Box 186)
    - PR 16-8 - Opinions-Statements-Questions or Articles, 1976 January 1 (Box 186)
    - PR 16-9 - Vice President's Name - Likeness (Box 186)
    - PR 16-10 - Sell to Vice President (Box 186)
    - PR 16-11 - Sit for Portrait, Sculptors, Pictures (Box 186)
    - PR 16-12 - Sponsorship-Patron-Honorary Chairman (Box 186)
    - PR 16-12 - Sponsorship-Patron-Honorary Chairman, 1976 January 1 (Box 186)
    - PR 16-13 - Presenting medals-pushing buttons (Box 186)
    - PR 16-15 - Requests for Flags flown over Capitol (Box 186)
    - PR 16-16 - Requests for items that VP has given as gifts to others (Box 186)
      Scope and Contents note
      Including Christmas gifts given to staff.
  - Publications (PU), 45
    - PU - PUBLICATIONS (Box 186)
    - PU 1 - Federal Agency (Box 186)
    - PU 1 - Federal Agency (by agency name)/A-Z (Box 186)
    - PU 1-1 - Congressional Directory (Box 186)
    - PU 1-2 - Congressional Record (Box 186)
    - PU 1-6 - Federal Releases from Agencies (Box 186)
    - PU 2 - Non-Federal Publications (Box 187)
    - PU 2-1 - Books - Booklets (Box 187)
    - PU 2-1 - Books - Booklets, 1975 July 1 (Box 187)
    - PU 2-2 - Cartoons (Box 187)
    - PU 2-3 - Clippings-Editorials (Box 187)
    - PU 2-3 - Clippings-Editorials, 1975 August 1 (Box 187)
    - PU 2-3 - Clippings-Editorials, 1976 January 1 (Box 187)
    - PU 2-4 - Magazines-Periodicals (Box 187)
    - PU 2-5 - Newspapers (Box 187)
    - PU 2-6 - Pornographic-Obscene literature (Box 187)
    - PU 3 - VP Confirmation hearing reports (Box 187)
  - Real Property (RA), 46
    - RA - REAL PROPERTY (Box 187)